//   -------- Jamaica - Easy Questions --------

const questionEasy = [
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the men's world record for the 100m sprint at 9.58 seconds?",
    easyA: "Usain Bolt",
    easyB: "Tyson Gay",
    easyC: "Adam Gemili",
    correct: "easyA",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which singer sung ‘No woman, no cry’ which was released in 1979?",
    easyA: "Kurt Cobain",
    easyB: "Bob Marley",
    easyC: "Michael Jackson",
    correct: "easyB",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which 1993 film is this quote from: 'Feel the rythm! Feel the rhyme! Get on up, it's bobsled time!",
    easyA: "Forrest Gump",
    easyB: "Toy Story",
    easyC: "Cool Runnings",
    correct: "easyC",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the secret service agent in the films ‘Spectre’ and ‘Casino Royale?’",
    easyA: "James Bond",
    easyB: "John Mason",
    easyC: "Mallory Kane",
    correct: "easyA",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a car produced by Austin/Rover?",
    easyA: "Montego",
    easyB: "Astra",
    easyC: "Mondeo",
    correct: "easyA",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these types of music uses steel drums?",
    easyA: "Rock",
    easyB: "Reggae",
    easyC: "Pop",
    correct: "easyB",
  },
    {
    question: "Which entrepreneur won investment on Dragon's Den with his famous Caribbean sauce?",
    easyA: "Levi Roots",
    easyB: "Shaun Pulfrey ",
    easyC: "Oscar Bezzant",
    correct: "easyA",
  },
    {
    question: "Which athlete won the women's 100m at London 2012?",
    easyA: "Carmelita Jeter",
    easyB: "Allyson Felix",
    easyC: "Shelly-Ann Fraser-Pryce",
    correct: "easyC",
  },
    {
    question: "Which British university has alumni including Lawrence Dallaglio & Gail Emms?",
    easyA: "Loughborough",
    easyB: "Bristol",
    easyC: "Kingston",
    correct: "easyC",
  },
      {
    question: "What beverage is shown on the Dunkin' Donuts logo?",
    easyA: "Wine",
    easyB: "Beer",
    easyC: "Coffee",
    correct: "easyC",
  },
];

//   -------- Barbados - Medium Questions --------

const questionMed = [
  {
    question: "Who sung ‘Umbrella’ in 2007 and ‘We Found Love?’ In 2011?",
    medA: "Rihanna",
    medB: "Ellie Goulding",
    medC: "Beyonce",
    correct: "medA",
  },
  {
    question: "Which aircraft reached speeds on 2,179 km/h?",
    medA: "Airbus A320",
    medB: "Concorde",
    medC: "Airbus Beluga",
    correct: "medB",
  },
  {
    question: "Which rum has the world’s oldest commercial distillery?",
    medA: "Captain Morgan",
    medB: "Kraken",
    medC: "Mount Gay",
    correct: "medC",
  },
  {
    question: "Which sport was believed to be first played in 1646?",
    medA: "Baseball",
    medB: "Cricket",
    medC: "Tennis",
    correct: "medB",
  },
  {
    question: "Where in London is the Worlds Smallest Police Station?",
    medA: "Trafalgar Square",
    medB: "Wembley Stadium",
    medC: "Camden Town",
    correct: "medA",
  },
  {
    question: "What are Silver Spoon known for making?",
    medA: "Sugar",
    medB: "Coffee",
    medC: "Tea",
    correct: "medA",
  },
  {
    question: "What are these types of? Angling, bait and fly",
    medA: "Swimming",
    medB: "Curling",
    medC: "Fishing",
    correct: "medC", 
  },
  {
    question: "Which two colours mix together to create green?",
    medA: "Blue and Yellow",
    medB: "Yellow and Red",
    medC: "Red and Blue",
    correct: "medA",
  },
  {
    question: "What sport famously takes place in the town of Ascot?",
    medA: "Archery",
    medB: "Horse Racing",
    medC: "Rugby",
    correct: "medB",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a three pronged spear?",
    medA: "Trident",
    medB: "Javelin",
    medC: "Glaive",
    correct: "medA",
  },
];

//   -------- Bermuda - Hard Questions --------

const questionHard = [
  {
    question: "Which musical by Lin-Manuel Miranda is mostly sung and rapped throughout?",
    hardA: "Hamilton",
    hardB: "Wicked",
    hardC: "Dear Evan Hansen",
    correct: "hardA",
  },
  {
    question: "Which ocean separates North America and the United Kingdom?",
    hardA: "Atlantic Ocean",
    hardB: "Pacific Ocean",
    hardC: "Indian Ocean",
    correct: "hardA",
  },
  {
    question: "Which rum is the trademark rum to use in a Dark 'N' Stormy Cocktail?",
    hardA: "Kraken",
    hardB: "Havana Club",
    hardC: "Goslings",
    correct: "hardC",
  },
  {
    question: "Which member of The Beatles was murdered?",
    hardA: "George Harrison",
    hardB: "John Lennon",
    hardC: "Paul McCartney",
    correct: "hardB",
  },
  {
    question: "Which vegetable is related to shallots and can be made into rings or bhajis?",
    hardA: "Tomato",
    hardB: "Courgette",
    hardC: "Onion",
    correct: "hardC", 
  },
  {
    question: "What TV show shown on Channel 4 strands contestants on an island to see how they survive?",
    hardA: "Castaway",
    hardB: "Shipwrecked",
    hardC: "The Hotel",
    correct: "hardB",
  },
  {
    question: "Which flag represents the United Kingdom?",
    hardA: "Union Jack",
    hardB: "Royal Standard",
    hardC: "Jolly Rodger",
    correct: "hardA",
  },
  {
    question: "Which football team has scored the fastest goal in Premier League history?",
    hardA: "Crystal Palace",
    hardB: "Manchester City",
    hardC: "Southampton",
    correct: "hardC",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these would you wear in hot weather?",
    hardA: "Chinos",
    hardB: "Jeans",
    hardC: "Shorts",
    correct: "hardC",
  },
  {
    question: "What shape can be an isosceles, equilateral, scalene or a right-angle?",
    hardA: "Square",
    hardB: "Triangle",
    hardC: "Circle",
    correct: "hardB",
  },
];